I Can Eat Glass:

And from the sublime to the ridiculous, here is a certain phrase in an assortment of languages:

Sanskrit: ﻿काचं शक्नोम्यत्तुम् । नोपहिनस्ति माम् ॥

Sanskrit (standard transcription): kācaṃ śaknomyattum; nopahinasti mām.

Classical Greek: ὕαλον ϕαγεῖν δύναμαι· τοῦτο οὔ με βλάπτει.

Greek (monotonic): Μπορώ να φάω σπασμένα γυαλιά χωρίς να πάθω τίποτα.

Greek (polytonic): Μπορῶ νὰ φάω σπασμένα γυαλιὰ χωρὶς νὰ πάθω τίποτα. 

Latin: Vitrum edere possum; mihi non nocet.

Old French: Je puis mangier del voirre. Ne me nuit.

French: Je peux manger du verre, ça ne me fait pas mal.

Provençal / Occitan: Pòdi manjar de veire, me nafrariá pas.

Québécois: J'peux manger d'la vitre, ça m'fa pas mal.